A Guide to the McCue Family Papers ca. 1767-1944
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: McCue Family Notebooks and Bound Volumes (Box 19 - M-27)
  - School Notebooks, etc., of C. Purcell McCue, Jr.
    - Notebook n.d., bound volume (Box 26)
      re Religion, Mathematics, and Geometry belonging to McDaniel Purcell
    - Notebook n.d., bound volume (Box 26)
      re Surgical Pathology belonging to McDaniel Purcell
    - Notebook 1884-1885, 2 volumes; bound volume (Othertype 27)
      re Treatment belonging to McDaniel Purcell
    - Notebook n.d., bound volume (Box 27)
      re Mineralogy belonging to Sam Purcell
    - Notebook 1872-1873, 2 volumes; bound volume (Othertype 27)
      re Chemistry belonging Lyon G. Tyler
    - Notebook 1872-1873, 1880, bound volume (Box 27)
      re Chemistry, Physics belonging Lyon G. Tyler
    - Account Books of John H. McCue 1834-1835, 1848-1852, 2 volumes; bound volume (Othertype 28)
    - Account Book of John H. McCue 1857-1869, bound volume (Box 28)
    - Bank Books, Notebooks, and Miscellaneous Small Volumes 1870-1875, 1903, bound volume (Box 28)
    - Notes kept by William T. McCue 1875, bound volume (Box 28)
    - Receipt Book of John H. McCue 1845-1848, bound volume (Box 28)
    - Record Book and Proscription Book of Dr. P.C. Irvine 1841-1854, bound volume (Box 28)
    - Scrapbooks n.d., 2 volumes; bound volume (Box 28)
    - Ledger with an index for C.W.P. & Company [Charles W. Purcell & Company] 1863-1879, 1884 (Othertype Ledger)
    - Architectural drawing in pencil by N.G. Starkwether n.d. (Oversize M-27)
      of a Wood House, with three privies and a garden tool shed on the left side, and a smoke house on the right side, drawn for E. Taylor